<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="leagueName">
        <item>Premier League</item>
        <item>La Liga</item>
        <item>Serie A</item>
        <item>Ligue 1</item>
        <item>Bundesliga</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="leagueLogo">
        <item>@drawable/premier_league</item>
        <item>@drawable/laliga</item>
        <item>@drawable/serie_a</item>
        <item>@drawable/ligue_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/bundesliga</item>
    </array>

    <array name="leagueBackground">
        <item>@drawable/premier_league_background</item>
        <item>@drawable/la_liga_background</item>
        <item>@drawable/serie_a_background</item>
        <item>@drawable/ligue_1_background</item>
        <item>@drawable/bundesliga_background_2</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="leagueId">
        <item>4328</item>
        <item>4335</item>
        <item>4332</item>
        <item>4334</item>
        <item>4331</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="leagueDetail">
        <item>
            The Premier League, often referred to as the English Premier League or the EPL outside England,
            is the top level of the English football league system.
            Contested by 20 clubs, it operates on a system of promotion and relegation with the English Football League.
        </item>
        <item>The Campeonato Nacional de Liga de Primera División, commonly known as La Liga,
            is the men\'s top professional football division of the Spanish football league system.</item>
        <item>
            Serie A, also called Serie A TIM due to sponsorship by TIM, is a professional league competition for
            football clubs located at the top of the Italian football league system and the winner is
            awarded the Scudetto and the Coppa Campioni d\'Italia.
        </item>
        <item>
            Ligue 1, also called Ligue 1 Uber Eats due to sponsorship by Uber Eats, is a French professional
            league for men\'s association football clubs. At the top of the French football league system,
            it is the country\'s primary football competition.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Bundesliga, sometimes referred to as the Fußball-Bundesliga or 1. Bundesliga, is a professional
            association football league in Germany. At the top of the German football league system,
            the Bundesliga is Germany\'s primary football competition.
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>